去死吧  加拉格
Fuck you, Gallagher.
反正这里热死了
Too hot in here anyway.
床单都黏在我背上
Sheets are sticking to my back.
而且我得去上班
And I gotta go to work.
你有个称职的爸爸就该偷着乐了
Be happy you have a real dad,
好过我那个偷钱酗酒
not some thieving alcoholic deadbeat
还爱在放银器的抽屉里呕吐的废物
who's puking into the silverware drawer.
我...
I--
过几天要把排污总管挖出来
Doin' some work on the sewer main in a couple days,
提醒你们一下
just wanted to warn ya.
提醒什么
Warn us what?
到时候会停水
The water's gonna be shut off for the day.
谢了
Oh, thanks.
亲爱的  这是什么
Honey? What is that for?
性爱秋千
Sex swing.
想试试能否同时承受我们两个人的重量
Trying to see if it can bear both of us at once.
要是不行的话  我就去弄个四脚架
If not, I can get us a four-post freestander.
天啊
Oh, God.
怎么了  这是...
What-- is this--
-我们不是...  -没事
- aren't we--? - It's fine.
就是这整个负载的事
It's just with all the, um, shipments and everything.
就是...没事啦
And just-- it's totally fine.
就是...
It's just--
我不太习惯  服从
I'm just not used to being, um, submissive.
明天可以让你主导啊
You can be the dom tomorrow.
好吧  很好
Okay. Oh, that's fine.
成熟一点
It's good for us to grow...
也好
as people.
浴室没人了  下一个谁来
Shower's free. Who's next?
她跟我们半点亲戚关系都没有
She's not even related to us.
去楼下尿吧  去吧
Go pee downstairs. Go.
你准备让茉莉在这待多久
How long do you plan on keeping Molly around?
直到我们找到人收留他
Till we find someone to take him in.
-你有在找吗  -有
- Are you looking? - Yeah.
很好  找的同时记得告诉"她"
Good. Might as well tell him he's a he,
"她"是个男孩
while you're at it.
几点了
Mm, what-- what time is it?
爱爱时间
Sex o'clock.
快点  赶在卡尔回来之前
Quick, before Carl gets back.
-不行  -我还在睡觉呢
- Yeah, no, I can't-- - I'm sleeping.
我得  帮卡尔准备日托
I got to, uh-- I gotta help Carl set up for day care.
那不是黛比的活儿吗
I thought that was Debbie's job.
确实是的
Yeah, no, it is.
但她今天要去泳池
She's just going to the pool today,
所以我答应帮她看场
so I promised I'd supervise.
我还在睡觉呢
Still sleeping.
你今天要干什么
What are your plans for the day?
我准备和小凯
Actually me and Kev are taking
开冰淇淋车去印第安纳州
the ice cream truck to Indiana,
弄点烟火回来
going on a fireworks run.
我们能去吗
Can we come?
不行  这么多人回来坐不下
Uh, no, we won't all fit on the way back.
光是烟火就要占掉
You know, stash is probably gonna take up,
大概半个车厢
like, half the truck, so--
明天再去不行吗
Can you do it tomorrow?
我想趁工作日人不多
I really want us to take Molly to the beach
带茉莉去沙滩玩
before the weekend meatheads descend.
天哪
Jesus.
要不要这么旁若无人啊
Other people exist, maybe?
不行  我得赶在罗马焰火筒
No, I gotta get down there
卖完之前过去
before the Roman candles sell out.
你找到茉莉的亲人了吗
Hey, did you find any, uh, Molly relatives?
在脸书上找到一个当海军的远房亲戚
Tracked down a second cousin in the Navy on Facebook.
你给他留言了吗
Did you post on his wall?
他的状态写着  任务出海
Status says he's on sea duty.
等他回来我就给他发
I'll do it when he gets back.
那要到什么时候
I mean, um, when's that?
状态里没写
Didn't say.
好吧
Okay.
把你的花洞藏起来  好吗
Look, cage the ferret, okay?
日托小孩的家长可不想大清早就见你的草丛
Day care parents don't appreciate morning muff.
给你  好狗狗
Here you go. Good doggy.
一百  一百秒
100. 100 seconds!
吉米  我没法同时做早餐  准备日托
Jimmy, I can't do breakfast, set up for day care,
还要练习憋气
and practice holding my breath all at the same time.
我手指还没好呢
Oh, it's still broken.
是手指  又不是脖子
It's a finger, not your neck.
卡尔  能准备一下日托吗
Carl, can you set up for day care?
我要上午九点准时到泳池
I need to get to the pool at exactly 9:00 AM.
-今天是开放日  -我在给利亚姆喂食
- It's opening day. - I'm feeding Liam.
我能帮忙
I can help.
谢了  茉莉
Thanks, Molly.
擦一下宝宝玩具桌和磨牙玩具
Okay, wipe down the exersaucers and teething toys,
再检查一下枕巾上有没有头虱和鼻屎
then check the nap-pads for head-lice and boogers.
这裙子美翻了
That's a really pretty dress.
它能遮住我的女生宝贝
It hides my girl penis.
妈妈说突出来一块不礼貌
Mom said it's impolite to show off my bulge.
再来点咖啡
More coffee?
利普  伊恩  快下楼
Lip, Ian, come down here a sec!
听好了  加拉格家的和米尔科威奇家的
Okay, listen up, Gallaghers and Milkoviches.
工人们过几天要把排污总管挖出来
They're digging up the sewer main in a few days
到时会断水
and shutting the water off,
我们得提前把衣服和碗给洗了
so we need to do laundry and dishes beforehand.
那上厕所怎么办
What about toilets?
到时候就别冲水了
I guess we just won't flush that day.
可以用水桶
Well, we could fill up buckets.
好恶心
Gross.
他是残了还是怎么
He crippled or something?
真是帮大忙了
So helpful.
结婚的感觉很好吧
Must be nice having a spouse.
等下  他们要挖草坪
Wait, they're digging up the lawn?
对
Yeah.
那金吉姑妈怎么办
What about Aunt Ginger?
来了
Incoming.
我会回来吃晚餐  振作起来  孩子
I'll be back for dinner. Buck up, kiddo.
没什么大不了  就是三观颠覆而已
No biggie, just my universe falling apart.
你好啊  伙计
Hey, there, fella.
咱们去上厕所吧
Let's go take the Browns to the Super Bowl, huh?
天啊
Jesus!
猜猜今天谁来了  城建的人
Guess who came by today. The city.
他们要把院子里的排污管挖出来
They're digging up the yard to work on the sewer line.
你得赶在他们之前把金吉姑妈找出来
You need to find Aunt Ginger before they do.
谁
Who?
那个社保支票一直被你拿去兑现的
The dead relative whose social security checks
死亲戚
you've been cashing.
当初是你埋了她  现在你得把她挖出来
You buried her, you unbury her.
-伸手  -走吧  小黛
- Hand. - Come on, Debs.
再见  弗兰克
Bye, Frank.
你不是在看我的鸡巴吧
You're not trying to look at my dick, are you?
没  才没有
No, no, I'm not.
我甚至都没有想你把阴茎
I'm not even thinking about your dick...
杵在我爸嘴里这事
in my dad's mouth.
-绝对没有  -行  那就别想了
- I'm not. - Good, then don't.
真的  没想
Yep. Not.
伊恩把老二杵你爸嘴里
Ian's dick was in your dad's mouth?
这是种修辞手法
It's a figure of speech.
就好比说  "不关你事
It's like saying, "None of your business.
你的老二在我爸嘴里杵着  哥们"
Your dick's in my dad's mouth, man."
谁会这么说
Who says that?
同性恋
Gay dudes.
-伊恩是同性恋吗  -不  不
- Is Ian gay? - No, no.
它是一种委婉说法
It was euphemistic.
那同性恋是不是都喜欢这么做
Is that what gay people like to do?
天哪  算了  我--
Jesus. Forget it. I'm-- okay.
对了  杰米
Oh, uh, Jamie.
你会用电动工具吗
You any good with power tools?
利普  我需要你帮忙
Hey, Lip, I need your help.
忙着呢
Oh, busy.
忙到没空帮你的老爹了吗
Too busy to help your old man?
是啊  这辈子都是
Yes, forever.
伊恩人呢
Hey, Ian?
他正准备去上班呢
He's getting ready for work.
这漆喷得真不错
Nice paint job.
穿鞋了吗
You got your shoes on?
穿了  怎么了
Yeah. Why?
我们要去希拉家一趟
We're going over to Sheila's.
得去拿点埃迪生前用的重型机械
Gonna grab some of dead Eddie's heavy-duty machines.
那位老兄就爱园艺设备
That fella loved lawn equipment.
但是我病了
But I'm sick.
我看你挺好的啊
You don't look sick to me.
癌症呢
Cancer?
诊所打过电话了
The clinic called.
那些药起作用了
The pills worked.
癌症没了  恭喜你啊
No more cancer. Congrats.
-我不会死了吗  -不会了
- I'm not dying? - No!
-我们能开个派对吗  -当然了
- Can we have a party? - You bet.
等我们把这个老婊子挖出来先
Just as soon as we dig up this old, dead crack whore.
来吧  我们走
Come on, let's go.
你是拉拉吗
Are you a lesbo?
不是
Um, no.
尽管我认识很多与同性个体
Although I know many people
有着恋爱关系的人
who have had relations with same sex individuals.
我相信所有人都有
I believe all people should have the right
自由恋爱的权利
to love whomever they choose.
即使现在在伊利诺伊州
And even though civil unions
民事结合已经合法  这还是不够的
are legal in Illinois, it isn't enough.
改变是可能的  只要从我们做
Change is possible. It starts with us and--
别再盯着我们看了  怪胎
Stop staring at us, freak bag.
长点奶子吧
And grow some tits.
听到没
You hear that?
他们在楼上大战着呢
They're going for the brass ring up there.
是我给他们指明了道路
I did that, showed them the way--
像黑暗里的一盏明灯
like a headlamp in a coal mine.
跟你说  弗兰克·加拉格深谙人性
You see, Frank Gallagher knows people.
我仅凭直觉就知道
I-I just intuit.
我有一学期还主修了
I was, uh-- I was a psychology major
心理学呢
for a semester.
-爸  -怎么了
- Dad? - Yeah?
这是什么
What's this?
这是给肛门吸的奶嘴
Uh, that's a pacifier for your anus.
他们早到了  弗兰克
They're early, Frank!
有人在吗
Hello.
你能去照看下宝宝吗
Can you be on baby duty?
外面像是来了一个神父和一个越战老兵
Looks like a priest with a 'Nam vet.
有人在吗
Hello?
是皮特神父
It's Father Pete.
他带一个需要临终关怀的修女过来
He's with a hospice patient, a nun.
圣史蒂文医院没有空位了
They're out of room at St. Steven's.
-抱好  -你好啊  海米
- Here. - Oh, Hymie.
很高兴再见到你  皮特神父
Hey, nice to see you again, Father Pete.
我也是  乔迪
And you too, Jody.
你好  我是乔迪
Hi, I'm Jody.
抱歉  屋子里乱糟糟的
I'm sorry about the mess.
我们忙着干别的事去了
We've just been a little preoccupied.
没事
Not at all.
小心  小心
Careful, careful.
我恐怕她将不久于人世
She's not long for this world, I'm afraid.
她发过缄默誓
She's taken a vow of silence,
所以你们不用担心她祷告时
so you don't have to worry about her
会吵着你们睡不着觉了
keeping you up all night with her praying.
-这是她的镇痛药  -好的  好的
- This is her pain medication. - Great, yeah.
还有  请务必保证她的iPad时刻有电
Oh, and make sure her iPad is always charged.
她玩愤怒的小鸟可以玩一整天呢
She can play Angry Birds till the cows come home.
那个
Oh, well--
那个是用来  约束过激病人的
that's just a, um, harness for patients.
棚屋钥匙呢
Uh, shed key?
冰箱上面  顶上
On the fridge, top of the fridge.
你身上怎么是橙色的
Why are you orange?
弗兰克
Frank?
我也不知道这代表什么
I don't know what it is, red,
但想到我开车穿过整个城市
but I feel less alone in the world
就能在这里找到你
knowing I can drive across town
弯腰整理着灌装鸡汤时
and find you here,
我就觉得不那么孤独了
bent over cans of chicken stock.
听我说  我很抱歉  真的
Look. I-I'm sorry. Truly.
我只是
I just--
你能原谅一个崩溃的人吗
Can you forgive a man who's falling apart?
哪怕是一点点
A little?
行
Yeah.
-我能吻你吗  -不行
- Can I kiss you? - No.
一下就好
Just a little.
听我说
So listen.
我想找人把我家给抢了
Um, I need somebody to rob my house,
希望你能帮忙
and I'm hoping you could help.
你要我去抢你的家
You want me to rob your house?
坎迪丝把房子的锁给换了
Candace changed the locks on the house--
那可是我的房子
my goddamn house.
而且她不让我回去
And she won't let me back in,
所以我需要有人来把我的东西偷出来
so I need someone to steal my stuff.
我要是亲自偷  周围的邻居可能会认出我
If I do it, the neighbors might recognize me.
你早间时分进去看上去就像搬家工人一样
You go in during daylight hours and you look like movers.
不会有事的
You'll be fine.
她通常会熬到凌晨三点
Look, she stays up till 3:00 AM
一边喝着香草伏特加一边看着搏飞的广告
drinking Stoli vanilla and watching bowflex ads.
她到下午才会清醒
She'll be unconscious until well past noon.
这对你来说也是相当合算的
Okay, this could be very lucrative for you.
房子里的东西随你拿
You can take anything you want.
来吧  都是上好保险了的
Come on, it's all insured.
我只想要两套我的阿玛尼西装
All I want are my two Armani suits,
卢西恩·弗洛伊德的画
my Lucien Freud,
还有我那瓶九零年的拉图
and my bottle of 1990 Chateau Latour Pauillac.
怎么样  行吗
What do you say? Will you do it?
-弗兰克  -怎么了  儿子
- Frank? - Yes, son?
为什么一个男人会把自己的老二
Why would a dude put his penis
放到另一个男人的嘴里
in another dude's mouth?
男人有时会发现他们真正的喜好
Well, sometimes men discover things about themselves
比如他们喜欢男性生殖器多过女性生殖器
like they prefer male genitalia to female genitalia.
等等  你是说有的男的喜欢舔老二
Wait. So some guys like to lick wieners?
我认为他们首先是被对方的外形所吸引
Well, I'm sure at first they're attracted to each other's build.
一旦两个搭上了
And once a connection gets made,
他们就会开始舔老二了
then the wieners get licked.
今天真热  是不是
It's a scorcher today, ain't it?
小黛  泳池怎么样
Hey, Debs, how was the pool?
很好  游泳尿布在哪
Great. Where are the swim diapers?
谢谢  九号过道
Thanks. Uh, aisle nine.
是你在我的收银机里放大头钉吗
Did you put tacks in my drawer?
我的小妹本该得到你那份工作的
My baby sister shoulda got your job.
我花了四个月时间来教她
It took my four months to teach her
给人口交时如何不呕出来  为了啥
how to swallow without gagging, and for what?
弱视又不是她的错
Yeah, it's not her fault she got a lazy eye.
她的家教很好
She was raised right.
她并不觉得自己高人一等
She don't think she's better than nobody.
你妹妹的事我很遗憾
I'm sorry about your sister,
但我还有五个孩子要养呢
but I got five kids to feed.
菲奥娜
Fiona?
没事  我们闹着玩呢
Oh, you know, just employee shenanigans.
有优惠券吗
You got coupons for this?
我有十一点的卵巢囊肿病例
I've got an 11:00 ovarian cyst,
十一点半的泌尿感染病例
an 11:30 UTI,
加上大厅里的儿童孕例要看
and a preteen pregnancy in the lobby.
所以你们能告诉我为什么
So can you tell me why you're here
两周前刚来  现在又来吗
when I just saw you two weeks ago?
我们都日得长茧了  可我还是怀不上
We've been bangin' like bunnies and I can't get pregnant.
我需要再做一次检查
I need another exam.
这改变不了什么
It won't change anything.
但你上回说我有怀孕的可能
But you said last time I had a chance of getting pregnant.
我相信我说的是你怀孕的可能很小
I believe I said you had very little chance.
我还说了  "极度不可能"
I also used the words, "Highly unlikely"
"非常不现实"
and "Wildly improbable. "
你害得我宝贝女儿空欢喜一场
You got my baby girl's hopes up for nothing.
对于复杂问题  我选择在措辞上
I chose to mitigate a difficult discussion
用更为乐观和积极的说法
with upbeat and positive phrasings.
老实说  我到底怀不怀得上
I need to know the truth. Can I have a damn baby or not?
这么说吧  你基本上是绝对怀不上
Put is this way, you have a 99. 999 chance
但凡事都有例外
of not getting pregnant, nothing is impossible.
你说是不是一个老二插到另一个老二里面去
So does, like, one penis go into the other penis?
当然了  基佬们发情的时候
Of course. When gay dudes get horny,
他们老二的洞洞是大开着的
their pee holes open.
游泳尿布
Swim diapers.
上帝保佑  我已经捞出两坨屎了
Thank God. I've already had to fish out two poops.
爸爸
Daddy!
你身上一股漂白粉的臭味
You stink like bleach.
是啊  我今天去游泳了
Yeah, I was at the pool today.
我憋了112秒呢
I stayed under for 112 seconds.
真有你的
Hey, good for you!
给那些一身梅毒的婊子们点颜色看看
Show those syphilis-ridden turbo sluts a thing or two.
她们觉得自己尿在泳池  泳池就是他们的
They think they own the water just 'cause they piss in it.
我们挖到东西了
We hit something.
那是什么味
What's that smell?
-排污管  -老天
- The sewer line? - Oh, man.
或许你应该用透明胶
You probably should patch that up
跟T恤把它补上
with some duct tape and a t-shirt.
臭死了
Aah, God.
你确定我们没挖错地方
You sure we're digging in the right spot?
我真不敢相信你老婆居然到你家来了
Man, I can't believe your wife actually came to your house.
我还以为小维会弄死她呢
I thought V was gonna rip her throat out.
你跟曼迪是怎么回事
Yo, so what's up with you and Mandy?
-你们俩看上去挺亲热的  -可能吧
- You guys seem tight. - I guess.
她太粘人了
She's gotten hella clingy.
你救了她那异装癖的弟弟
You rescued her cross-dressing sibling.
简直就跟电影里演的一样
You swashbuckled that shit, man.
这下她算是死心塌地要跟你了  说真的
Seals the deal for a chick, I'm serious.
女孩子们就喜欢这类英雄救美的情节
Girls take that hero crap straight to the bank.
她现在是不是帮你做饭  帮你叠衣服
She cook for you now? Fold your clothes?
有时吧
Sometimes.
她一周在你那里待的时间超过四晚
She stay over more than four nights a week?
不管什么都帮你
Help you out with random stuff?
老兄  你这算是结婚了  好好享受吧
Dude, you are ghetto married. Enjoy it.
你能享受一切好处  还不用负责
You get all the perks, no paperwork.
有些人想要还来不及呢
Guys would kill for that setup.
我倒是有点烦了
I kinda hate it.
你是怎么了  老兄
What's wrong with you, man?
我觉得是凯伦伤你太深了
I think Karen messed you up bad.
点火
Gun it.
干得好
Ah, good work.
办事利索点  女士
Get your act together, lady.
我这有一天前的颈肉  两天前的西冷牛排
I got day-old chuck, two-day-old sirloin,
几块半硬不软的百吉饼
couple of partially soft bagels,
还有两加仑快过期的蛋黄酱
and, like, two gallons of nearly expired mayo.
外加一块蛋糕
Oh, and a sheet cake.
乔尼接孩子又迟到了
Joanie was late picking up her kid again.
猜猜这次的理由是什么
And guess what the excuse was.
-爆胎  -爆胎
- Flat tire? - Flat tire.
困扰我的不是同性恋的问题
It's not the homo thing that gets me,
基佬经常看上我  我一点都不反感
'cause gays hit on me all the time and it doesn't bother me.
他们当然喜欢你  你穿合身的牛仔裤
Of course they do. You wear designer jeans
头上擦一堆有的没的
and coconut hair product.
你简直就是基佬杀手
You're like gay flypaper.
猪你生日快乐
"Haddy Birthday Juby? "
蛋糕店那家伙有诵读困难症
Bakery guy is dyslexic.
-弗兰克在哪  -没见到他
- Where's Frank? - Haven't seen him.
他得把外面埋金吉的坑填上  臭死了
Well,he's gotta fill in that hole where Ginger was, it reeks out there.
他忘了把她埋哪了
He forgot where he buried her.
你开玩笑的吧
You're kidding.
我们找不到她
We couldn't find her.
卡尔还把排污管砸坏了
And Carl busted the sewer line.
又开始弹吉他了吗
Wait. You picking up guitar?
同事们找我麻烦
Bitches at work giving me shit.
在我收银机里放大头针  相信吗
Thumb tacks in my change drawer. You believe that?
-我操  -没错
- Holy shit. - Yep.
是的  我们做的很好
Yeah,we did good.
新兴的小城对我们不薄
Boomtown was good to us.
要去炸汉考克中心吗
Blowing up the Hancock Building?
不  卡车里装不下了
No, we don't have any more room in the truck.
能放点在这吗
Can we store some here?
你疯了  看看这孩子的脸
Are you nuts? Look at that kid's face.
我保证会藏到卡尔碰不到的地方
I promise I'll put it in a no-Carl zone.
如果那个地方存在的话
As if that exists.
-别碰它  -洗脸去  纵火狂
- Don't touch it. - Go wash your face, pyro.
曼迪  别闲着  把餐具摆好
Mandy, make yourself useful. Set the table.
要汽水  啤酒还是冰水
You want pop, beer, or ice water?
水就行  谢谢
Water's good. Thanks.
把这些放到利普的床上
Put these on Lip's bed.
-她一周内就走人  -哪一个
- She's out in a week,okay? - Which one?
吉米抽什么风  因为他爸的事吗
What's with Jimmy? That shit with his dad?
他是挺受打击的
He's pretty broken up about it.
没人死  没人受伤  没人蹲监狱
No one's dead,wounded,or incarcerated.
你还指望什么
What do you expect?
城北来的富家公子
Rich kid from the North Side--
这是他人生中的第一次重大的家庭危机
It's his first big family crisis.
他有点难接受
He's taking it pretty hard.
你嘴巴左边有东西
Left side of your mouth.
另一边才是
Other left.
这家伙也有"老爸问题"  怪不得你中意他
Dude's got daddy issues. No wonder you dig him.
我听得见你们说话
I can hear you.
利普  去整理下卡车
Hey, Lip, go reorganize the truck.
把大麻放到冰箱里  爆竹放到冷冻室里
Put the weed in the fridge, poppers in the freezer.
烟火摆到上面  鞭炮藏到座位底下
Put the smokes on top and the bangers underneath the seats.
-好的  -我去帮忙
- Yep. - I'll help.
-晚饭吃蛋糕吗  -我得去趟酒吧
- Cake for dinner? - I gotta get to the Alibi.
大夫早上怎么说
Hey, what did the doc say this morning?
没时间去医院
Never had a chance to go.
好吧  我爱你
Okay. I love you.
-找代孕妈妈怎么样  -你要做吗
- What about a surrogate? - You offering?
才不
Hell no.
你在分类广告上肯定能找到合适的
Bet you could find someone good on Craigslist.
要给她钱  试管婴儿医生也要钱
Bitch gets paid, IVF docs gets paid,
医疗账单  孕妇装  律师费  合同费
medical bills, maternity clothes, lawyer fee, contract fees.
最少  也要4万
Low end? 40 grand.
得玩好久的角色扮演才能攒够
Need a truckload of slave-play to raise that kinda scratch.
-你打算怎么办  -想办法吧
- What'll you do? - Something.
修女  我很敬佩你的誓约
Sister, I so admire the vow you've taken.
拒绝诱惑需要强大的定力
It takes such strength to resist the lure of temptation,
口头或是行动上都是
verbally or otherwise.
修女  我真抱歉
Oh, sister, I'm-I'm so sorry.
乔迪和我在尝试一些新东西
Jody and I are just experimenting with new liberties.
你知道  我们的身体是上帝的神庙
As you know, our bodies are God's temple,
我们只是想为它添一双翅膀
and it's as if we're adding on a little wing or two.
你是绝对不会在说话了吧
So there's no way in the world you would ever talk?
修女呀
Oh, sister.
乔迪将我推向一个新的阶段
Jody is pushing me to new levels.
这完全是我的错误
It's completely my fault.
他警告过我  不要触及他的底线
He warned me not to go through this gateway with him,
但我没有听
but I wouldn't listen.
现在  我已无路可退了
And now I can't find my way back.
我的身体从来没有一次性
I've never had so many things inserted into
插入过这么多东西
so many parts of my body at once!
我是否在鼓励他突破自己的极限
Have I encouraged him to overstep his boundaries?
还是在帮助他创造一个全新的更健康的自我
Or am I helping him to create new and-and healthy ones?
我承认
Because I admit,
遭受性爱的蹂躏
inflicting sexual pain
带给我更多的快感
gives me great pleasure.
你准备好了吗  妈咪  电池充满电了哟
You ready, mama? Batteries are charged!
修女  我感觉好多了
Oh,sister,I feel so much better.
谢谢你听我倾诉
Thank you for letting me get that off my chest.
你真是好人
Oh,you're a good one.
为什么戴手套
Gloves?
工作的时候手划破了
Got some cuts on my hands at work.
已经擦干了
I think it's dry.
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
老天  我刚意识到
Oh, my God. I just realized.
爸爸和沃德先生打的那场架
That huge fight that dad had with Mr. Ward,
沃德是我七年级的基佬理科老师
my gay seventh grade science teacher--
我原以为是因为
I thought it was because of
我在面包酶项目上得分太差
the crappy grade I got on my bread mold project,
但他们一直要求私下讨论这个问题
but they kept on excusing themselves to discuss it in private.
我真是个白痴
I am such an idiot.
还有高中的时候
And that wedding
我们一家去夏威夷参加的那场婚礼
that we went to in Hawaii
我  妈妈和奇普早早就上床休息了
when I was in high school-me,mom,and Chip went to bed early
但老爸他和伴郎跳了整晚的舞
and dad stayed up dancing all night with the best man.
我觉得  真正困扰我的
I guess what really gets
是他没告诉我真相
me is that he couldn't tell me the truth.
他是以为我会不接受他
I mean,did he think I wouldn't accept him
还是我会因此看扁他
or that I'd think less of him?
他为什么不信任我
Why didn't he trust me?
我是唯一不知情的那个吗
Am I the only one who didn't know?
我哥知道吗
Does my brother know?
我打赌我哥一定知道
Oh, I bet you my brother knows.
等等  还有干屁眼的情节吗
Wait, so there's butthole involved?
有时候有  不一定
Sometimes, not always.
伊恩和我准备抽点大麻然后看恶搞之家
Ian and I are gonna go get high and watch Family Guy.
你要来吗
You wanna come?
不  开了一天车  累死了
Uh, no, I've been driving all day. I'm exhausted.
晚上洗衣服  有要洗的吗
Doing a night load. Any takers?
给你
Here you go.
-没有吗  利普  -下午我把我们的洗了
- Lip,nothing? - Did ours this afternoon.
也许下次你可以把黛比或者卡尔
Maybe next time you wanna throw in
或者利亚姆的一起洗了
Debbie or Carl or Liam's with yours.
当然  没问题
Sure, no problem.
如果你改变主意  就下来  好吗
Hey, if you change your mind, come down, okay?
我得知道  同性恋是怎么性交的
I need to know where the gay wieners go.
你记得厕所堵了是怎么通的吗
You know how you plunge a toilet when it's backed up?
记得
Yeah.
想象成一个男人在通另一个男人的厕所
Think of it as one dude plunging another dude's toilet.
可以领养啊
Could always adopt.
我不想要别人的孩子
I don't want someone else's kid.
我希望宝宝能继承
I want a little punk with
你漂亮的眼睛和狡黠的微笑
your pretty eyes and your crooked smile.
我不知道  小维
I don't know, V, at some point
也许我们得接受  这就是命
we might have to accept that it's not meant to be.
命
Not meant to be?
我17岁的时候被强奸  染上性病不能生育
Was I meant to get an STD at 17 from some lame-ass rapper
是命吗
that would trash my tubes?
当我在网上查了他一下午
Was I meant to Google him all afternoon
发现他有8个孩子是命吗
to find out he has eight kids?
我在脸书上加他好友  给他留言
Was I meant to friend him on Facebook
控诉他毁掉我的生活也是命吗
to write on his wall some psychotic rant about how he ruined my life?
-宝贝  没事的  -不  不是
- Baby, it's okay. - No, it's not.
操他妈
Fuck his weak-ass rhymes,
操那些赤脚庸医
fuck that tree frog-lookin' doctor,
操我过去20年花在
and fuck all the fuckin' money I spent on condoms
套子上的钱
for the last 20 years.
还有你  操你这
And fuck you for acting like you don't wanna
-逆来顺受的态度  -等等
- fight harder for this. - Whoa.
你知道我有多想要孩子
You know I do, more than anything.
那我们就继续努力吧
Then let's fight.
别踢了
Enough with the kicking!
-上帝啊  -她在哪
- Christ! - Where is she?
不行  我放弃了
I can't-- I give up.
我要睡觉
I need sleep.
我来和你缕一缕
Let me spell this out for you.
城建局如果挖出了遗骸
The city digs up some bones.
警察就会来
The police show up.
他们查出那是金吉姑妈的
They figure out it's Aunt Ginger.
他们去确定遗骸的年代
They date the bones.
他们发现她已经死了14年
They realize she's been dead for 14 years.
然而  她的社保支票
And yet, her social security checks
却月月都有人兑现
are being cashed every month.
这不是醉酒驾驶  弗兰克
This isn't a DUI, Frank.
你埋了一具尸体
You buried a body and you stole
并窃取联邦政府的资产
from the Federal Government.
你会蹲一辈子监狱
You will never get out of prison.
想想吧
Think about it.
该死
Fuck.
你记得那个
Hey. You know the guy
在夜店外被你海扁的家伙吗
you beat the shit out of at that club?
他想让我潜入他的大宅
He wants me to sneak into his mansion,
帮他拿点东西
take all of his crap.
真的
Really?
滑稽
Hilarious.
他自己不能去  闹离婚
He can't get it himself. Divorce.
说我可以随便拿
Says I can take whatever I want.
他很有钱  你想去吗
He's loaded. You want in?
天呐   用空包弹行不行
Jesus! Use blanks, maybe?
该死
Fuck.
能带我表兄弟们去吗
Can I bring my cousins?
-可以  -那好
- Yeah. - All right.
我去
I'm in.
真不明白你怎么会看上
I don't know what you see
那个靠吃伟哥才能上膛的老头子
in that geriatric viagroid.
他给我买东西  给我点客房服务
He buys me stuff, orders me room service.
不怕跟我接吻
He isn't afraid to kiss me.
大麻烟卷快要卖完了
Yeah, we're low on joints.
冰箱里还有一些大麻叶
I got extra weed in the fridge,
但还没卷
but it needs rolling.
你们看上去好像需要帮助
You guys look like you could use some help.
-是的  太好了  -不  不需要  谢谢
- Yeah, that'd be great. - No, we're good, thanks.
能帮我们卷点大麻烟卷吗
Can you roll us some spliffs?
好啊  需要一些纸
Sure. We need papers.
在那儿呢
Right there.
你俩真牛
You guys are really killing it.
哇哦  大巨人
Whoa, you are a giant.
要是敢问我是不是打篮球的
Ask me if I play basketball
我就打碎你的蛋蛋
and I'll punch your nuts.
买点啥
What do you want?
两个烟火  一包仙女棒
Two fountains, a pack of sparklers,
三卷大麻  一根冰棍
three joints, and a bomb pop.
你还需要去做社区服务吗
Hey, you got any community service hours left?
怎么了
Why?
茉莉可以帮忙  他主动要求的
Molly could help, he offered.
不用了  我都搞定了
No. You know what? I'm covered.
这里也没啥事了  你可以回家了
Actually we're good here too. You can go home.
让她在这待着吧
You know what? Have her stick around.
我马上要回酒吧了
I gotta hit the Alibi in ten minutes away.
-我自己能行  -我想待在这
- I can handle it. - I'm good to stay.
不用了  你还是回家吧  曼迪
No, please just go home, Mandy--
好歹回一次你自己那个破家吧
to your own fucking house, for once.
真伤人啊
That was harsh.
不是吧  姐妹们
Really, ladies?
很好笑
Really funny.
我是菲奥娜
Hi, this is Fiona.
是二号收银员
I'm working register two.
我被锁在厕所了
I'm locked in the bathroom.
我已经拧过把手了
I did try the knob.
好吧  我再试试
Fine. I'll try again.
哪里让你觉得可以在
On what planet is it cool for you
员工卫生间抽烟啊
to take a smoke break in the employee bathroom?
我都不抽这牌子好吧
I don't even smoke Parliaments.
恭喜你发育了
Holy crap, congrats on your puberty.
是啊  小咪咪看起来不错
Yeah, your tits look great.
谢谢
Thanks.
俗话说的好变化总一夜之间
You know, they always say it happens overnight.
去游泳吧
Go for a swim.
去试试你的新身体
Try out your new bod.
好啊
Okay.
这才第四杯
It's my fourth.
第四十四杯我都不管
I don't care if it's your 44th.
我们不能退
We don't do buybacks.
-我穷死了  -小公主  新鲜消息
- I'm broke. - Hey, news flash, princess.
来这儿喝酒的百分之一百五都是穷鬼
So is 150% of the patronage here.
你来啦  欢迎回来
Oh, there she is. Welcome back.
假期怎么样
How was your vacay?
我去冲浪了  被水上摩托撞了
Oh, I went surfing, got hit by a jet ski,
-还看见海豚自慰  -是吗
- saw a dolphin masturbate. - Yeah?
我手指断了  父母要离婚
Well, my finger's broken, my parents are divorced,
-我爹是个男同性恋  -男同性恋
- and my dad's a fairy, so-- - A fairy?
你好  老古董
Hello, 1983.
我要的二氧化碳罐拿来了吗
Did you get my CO2 tanks?
嗯  你能快点吗
Yeah. Hey, can you make it quick?
我要出去
I gotta get out of here.
-好  好  -谢啦
- Yeah, yeah. - Thank you.
说实话  别介意
You know, not for nothin', but, uh,
没人喜欢听一个大男人抱怨
no one likes to hear a grown man whine.
就像男人穿UGG一样
It's like the verbal equivalent of a dude wearing UGGs.
感谢你的关心  谢谢了
Yeah, well, I appreciate the sympathy, thanks.
赶紧振作吧
Get over it.
菲奥娜没精力操心你这些事
Fiona doesn't have room for it.
她为了家里不断粮已经够忙的了
She's busting her ass just to keep food on the table.
库克县的好市民啊
Good denizens of Cook County,
我有一个提议
I have a proposition.
你他妈又要干嘛  弗兰克
What the fuck is it now, Frank?!
你们记得吗
Do you remember--
记得92年南阿什兰的
do you remember the holdup
珠宝店持枪抢劫案吗
of that jewelry store on South Ashland in '92?
当然记得
Oh, yeah, sure.
那些混蛋把可怜的西班牙人
Bastards cleaned out these poor spics
抢了个精光
of every piece of crap that they had.
是我妈干的
That was my mother.
抢劫的是她
She did the heist.
我觉得她把抢的东西埋在我家后院了
And I think she buried the crap in my backyard.
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
她藏在了某个地方
Well, she stashed it somewhere
然后她忘了是哪儿
and then she forgot where.
那天我在种罗勒[一种调料]
So the other day I was planting some basil.
最近我又开始做园艺了
I've recently gotten back into gardening.
然后  我发现了这个
And I found this.
我操  是金子吗
Shit, is that gold?
有可能
Could be.
很脏  得拿去鉴定
Pretty dirty, gotta get it appraised.
重点是
The point being,
这只是花园宝藏的冰山一角
this is only the tip of the golden iceberg.
我不能一个人挖完整个花园
Now I can't dig it all up by myself.
如果谁愿意和我一起挖
So I will give a sizeable cut
我可以给他相当大的分成
to anyone who helps me unearth it.
有人报名吗
So who's with me?
-去他妈的  不妨一试  -我加入
- Fuck it. Why not? - I'm in.
给力  太赞了  勇士们
There you go. Bravo, soldiers.
前进  前进  咱们走
Onward, onward. Let's go.
-放手去干  -就是要这种精神
- Let's do it. - That's the spirit.
使美利坚强大的精神
This is what made America great.
大姨妈  大姨妈来了
Ew, period! Period!
游泳馆咋样
Hey. What'd I miss at the pool?
我们应不应该
Should we--
再确定一下我们是否真的别无选择了
Let's just make sure we explored all other options.
好
Okay.
以前和你一起工作那个佣人怎么样
What about that maid you used to work with?
桑卓  太疯了
Chantrelle? Too crazy.
原来养老院的梅西呢
How about Macie down at the old folks home?
-瘾君子  -菲奥娜呢
- Too medicated. - Fiona?
太白了
Too white.
真的  你还考虑这种事
Really? Is that a concern of yours?
我希望他能遗传到我的特质
I want it to have my genetic material,
起码要看起来像
or at least look like it does.
你表姐莎朗达呢
What about your cousin Sharonda?
我今早打给她了
I called her this morning.
她酒瘾又犯了  中午就已经醉的不行了
She fell off the wagon, was fried by noon.
你其他表姐妹呢
Well, what about your other cousin?
就是那个  挺漂亮的那个
You know, the, uh, pretty one?
漂亮的
Oh, the pretty one?
没有  我只是想让我们的孩子像你一样美
No, 'cause I want our kid to look pretty like you.
-我是说  -她才13岁
- I mean-- - She's 13.
看起来比较成熟
She seems older.
天啊
Aah. Jesus.
圣母玛利亚啊  臭死了
Mother of Christ, it stinks.
这里屎也太多了
There's so much shit in the yard.
闭嘴赶紧挖吧
Shut up and keep digging.
独臂大侠都比你挖的快
The one arm wonder's making more progress than you.
你就挖了这么点啊
This is as far as you got?
别指手画脚的
Don't judge!
弗兰克  你确定珠宝
Frank, do you know for certain
是被埋在这儿吗
there's jewelry buried out here?
知道吗
Uh, you know what?
试试那边的栅栏
Try along that fence there.
我看到过她像只獾一样在那儿翻来翻去
I saw her rootin' around in there like a badger.
你这是要参加芝士蛋糕工厂的沙漠风暴之夜吗
Is it desert storm night at the Cheesecake Factory?
1991年以美国为首的多国部队
开始实施“沙漠风暴”行动  海湾战争爆发
你为什么那么对曼迪
Why are you acting like a dick to Mandy?
我认为这件事儿
I think that qualifies as
不他妈关你的事
none of your fuckin' business.
她从她姨妈家打给我
Well, she called me from aunt's house,
说是你叫她滚回家
said you told her to go home.
茉莉也要走吗
Is Molly leaving too?
什么  不会的小黛  听着哥们儿
What? No, Debs. Look, man.
她缠着问  问我晚上的安排
She is always on me about, you know, our plans for the night
或者什么时候去看她朋友乐队的表演
and when we're going to see her friend's band
还有下星期要干嘛
and what we're doing next week.
她喜欢和你呆在一起怎么了
So she likes hanging out with you.
-这又不犯法  -我喜欢茉莉
- That's not a crime. - I like Molly.
她又不是我老婆
She's not my wife.
对  但是她是个对你好的女人
No, she's a good person who does nice things for you.
怎么  你成了她律师吗
What are you, her fuckin' lawyer?
不  我是她最好的朋友
No, I'm her best friend.
你现在表现出一副混蛋样子
All right, and you're acting like a douche bag.
不想好了  就结束
You want out? End it.
还想继续在一起
You don't?
就别对她那么差
Stop treating her like garbage.
别因为凯伦玩弄你
But just 'cause Karen wiped her ass with you
你就以为也可以这么对曼迪
doesn't give you the right to shit on Mandy.
坏消息  今晚咱们都要出去挖
Guys, bad news. We all gotta dig tonight.
市政府的人要来了  弗兰克还是找不到金吉姑妈
The city's coming and Frank can't find aunt Ginger.
所以呢
So?
如果我们找不到她  有人就要坐牢
So someone's going to jail if we don't find her.
你的意思是弗兰克要坐牢
Yeah, Frank, you mean.
我们都知道院子里有尸体
There's a body. We know about it.
我们都是共犯
We're accomplices.
又要给他擦屁股了
Once again saddled with a mess we didn't create.
我们越早出去开挖
Sooner we get out there and dig,
这事才能越快结束
the sooner it'll all be over.
我手上昨天的水泡还没消呢
I still got blisters on my hand from yesterday.
我可以挖啊
I can dig.
作为一个女孩  我的上臂很有劲儿
I have pretty developed upper arms for a chick.
借我烤火鸡的滴油管用用
I need to borrow your turkey baster.
我不想让茉莉走
I don't want Molly to leave!
她怎么了
What's with her?
今天在游泳馆来大姨妈了
She got her period at the pool today.
我都迫不及待想来大姨妈了
I can't wait to get my period.
妈妈说那是身体对女性牺牲的致敬
Mom said it's the body's tribute to female sacrifice.
你不是女孩  亲爱的
You're not a girl, honey.
你是个男孩
You're a boy who was raised
只是你那个磕药磕傻的妈
by a jacked-up meth head of a mom,
一直把你当女孩
who made you think you were a girl
因为她讨厌男人
because she hates men.
我不是女孩子
I'm not a girl?
利普
Lip.
黛比
Debbie?
那不是大姨妈
It wasn't real.
是番茄酱
It was ketchup.
她们在大庭广众之下整我
They did it in front of everyone!
-谁啊  -泳池的那些女孩
- Who? - The girls at the pool.
小黛
Debs.
她们好漂亮  男孩子都看她们
They're pretty and boys notice them.
但是她们美不了几天了
Well, they won't be pretty for long.
她们会走错路
They're gonna make all the bad decisions
你可以从她们的错误中得到经验
and you're gonna get to learn from their mistakes.
为什么她们那么刻薄
Why do they have to be so mean?
有些女孩子就是混蛋
Some girls are just jerks.
就像昨天店里那些贱人
Like that chick at the store yesterday.
我活该吗  不
Did I deserve that? No.
但是我就怕了她吗  没门儿
But did I take her shit? No way.
因为我强得多  你也是
'Cause I'm better than that and so are you.
谁都别想惹我们加拉格家的人
Nobody fucks with the Gallaghers.
黛比
Debbie?
走开
Go away.
开门
Open the door.
快别哭了
Come on.
我们得去挖土
We gotta dig.
我的看护人之罪
每日祷告博客
我们一起祈祷吧
请原谅她的罪
肉体的软弱
你不是发誓要保持沉默吗
I thought you took a vow of silence.
沉默不包括在网上的部分吗
The silence doesn't include the internet?
你每天都发布关于我的博客吗
You have been blogging about me every day?
我觉得我要吐了
I think I'm gonna puke.
用点劲儿  我们必须找到她
Muscle through it. We gotta find her.
卡尔去哪儿了
Where'd Carl go?
-忍者  -卡尔  不要
- Ninja! - Carl! No!
不
No!
-天啊  -该死  卡尔
- Oh, my God. - Shit, Carl!
那好像还真起作用了
That actually kinda worked.
你是从烟花储藏点偷来的吗
You get those from the fireworks stash?
-是的  -再去多拿一些吧
- Yeah. - Go get some more.
伊恩
Ian?
这边真是臭死了
Reeks out here.
听着
Listen.
老兄
Oh, man.
关于我爸的那些事  我...
About all the stuff, just with my dad, I--
天啊  我们为什么还在谈这事儿啊
Oh, my God, why are we still talking about this?
不是吧  天啊
I mean, really? Christ.
好吧  无论你何时需要我
Okay, so, like, whenever you need me
我都在你身边陪着你  但我只是需要你一次
I'm, like, there for you, but the one time I need you,
你就像是让我  滚远点吗
you're like, "Screw off"?
卡尔觉得自己是个癌症幸存者
Carl thinks he's a cancer survivor.
茉莉觉得自己是个长了阴茎的女孩
Molly thinks she's a girl with a penis.
黛比在公共游泳池被人欺负
Debbie's getting terrorized at the public pool.
我们家后院闻着跟臭水沟一样
This yard smells like a sewer.
我还有三个醉醺醺的混蛋
I got three drunk assholes
在我身后开着大机器作业
operating power tools behind me.
而且我的那些贱人同事
And the bitches at work
今天把我关在了洗手间里
locked me in a bathroom today.
我们现在都面临着蹲监狱的危险
And we might all be on the verge of going to prison.
你想谈吗  行
So you wanna talk? Fine.
拿一把铲子
Grab a shovel.
你就夸夸其谈吧  关于你父亲
Talk your face off about how your dad
是如何给一个青少年口交的
gave a blowjob to a teenager,
但你谈的时候也必须挖
but dig while you do it.
你知道吗
You know what?
我真的厌倦了玩这种
I'm really tired of playing this
"我的悲剧比你更悲剧"的游戏
"My tragedy is bigger than your tragedy" Game.
我的整个世界都被颠覆了
My entire world got rocked,
而你似乎根本都没意识到这一点
and it's, like, not even on your radar.
我们是恋人啊
We're in a relationship!
对我来说重要的  对你也该是重要的
What's important to me should be important to you.
瞧瞧我们
Look at us.
我们真的是在挖尸体
We are literally digging up a body.
你的遭遇能跟我们的相比吗
How do you even compare our situations?
那真好啊
Oh, that's great.
就那样走开
Walk away.
真是懦弱的举动
That's a real pussy move.
你何不去向你的同性恋父亲哭诉呢
Yeah, why don't you go cry to your gay dad about it?
我就怀胎十月
So I'll just be carrying it
等孩子一出世  你们就接过去
and you two take it from me when it comes out?
-是啊  妈  -上苍都知道
- Yes, mama. - 'Cause lord knows
我这么大年纪  实在没法儿养个孩子了
I am too old to be raising an infant.
那会是我们的孩子
It will be our child.
会是你的孙子
It will be your grandchild.
你当年可真是个乖宝宝
Aw, you were such a sweet baby.
但是天啊  你吃相可差劲了
But lord, were you a terrible eater.
你会把奶都溅到头发上  鼻子上
It'd get all up in your hair and in your nose--
没什么问题吧
Everything okay?
没事  稍等一下
Yeah, just a second.
我到"高潮"部分了
Oh, this comes the tricky part.
也没射多少吗
Not much in there.
我们其实用点眼药器就可以了
We could've used an eyedropper.
天啊  凯文
Jeez, Kevin.
好吧
Okay.
全部弄进去
Bottoms up.
比我想象得要温热一点
Warmer than I expected.
好了  大伙儿  该睡觉了
Okay, bedtime, gang.
我们明早再继续
We'll start again in the morning.
操
Fuck.
别担心你那笨蛋男友
Don't worry about your dweeb.
他只是躲开去舔伤口去了
He's just off licking his wounds.
他会回来的
He'll be back.
我们加拉格家的人真会选人  对吧
We Gallaghers sure know how to pick 'em, huh?
明早见
See you in the morning.
嘿  凯伦  我是利普
Hey, Karen. It's Lip.
我只是想告诉一下你最近的情况
Um, just wanted to give you an update--
不管你他妈在哪儿
wherever the fuck you are.
你的孩子  他现在很好
Um, your kid, he's doing great.
你妈妈和你前夫  他们...
Um, your mom and ex-husband, they're--
他们也很好
they're also doing great.
我爸爸  就是和你上床的那位
My dad, who you fucked,
他也很好  而且
he's doing great. And, um--
我现在真的很好很好
I'm doing really, really great--
我说出来  以免你想知道
just in case you were wondering.
你个自私  无知  可憎的狗屎
You selfish, ignorant, heinous piece of dogshit.
谢谢你离开  并且再也不回来
Thank you for leaving and never coming back.
你  我们都感谢你这样做
You-- we all owe you a huge fucking favor!
你太牛逼了
You rock.
嘿  要进去吗
Hey. Go inside?
把铲子也拿着
Bring that with you.
快
Come on.
嘿  是我
Hey, it's me.
我只是想知道你在哪儿
Uh, just wondering where you are.
给我短信或电话吧  再见
Call, text, whatevs. Bye.
我是说  难怪她抓狂了
I mean, no wonder she flipped out.
她肩负的压力和责任实在太大了
I mean, she's got so much on her plate.
她需要我在她身边陪着她
She needs me there for her.
不过  我也得处理好自己的问题
I--you know, I gotta work on my stuff too.
是啊  你真是太难了
Si. So hard for you.
可怜的史蒂夫
Poor Stevie.
你准备好再来一炮了吗
You ready to go again?
是啊
Yeah.
操
Fuck.
我是个混蛋
I'm a dick!
曼迪
Mandy?
我是个混蛋
I'm a dick.
你能下来吗
Can you come down?
我不是泄欲工具
I'm not a tool.
是啊  我知道
Yeah, I know.
你不能把我当工具对待
So you don't get to treat me like one.
我知道
I know.
下来吧
Come down.
求你了
Please?
伙计们  伙计们
Guys, guys.
别带枪  行吗
No fucking guns, all right?
里面只是个喝醉的老妇人
It's just a drunk old lady in there.
来  来  拿过来
Come on. Come on.
操
Fuck.
黛比哪儿去了
Where's Debbie?
她去泳池了
She's at the pool.
我们得继续挖
We gotta keep digging.
快用力
Oh, come on.
操
Oh, fuck.
老天啊
Jesus Christ.
小混蛋们
Fuckers!
操
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
-快跑  -混蛋们
- Go! - Fuckers!
-操  -操
- Fuck! - Fuck!
该死的
Fucking--
不可能吧
No fucking way!
操  操蛋的奈德
Fuck! Fucking Ned!
你也操他了吗
Are you fucking him too?
快他妈开车
Fucking drive.
你中枪了  米奇
You got shot, Mickey!
是的  我他妈当然知道我中枪了
Yes, I fucking know I got shot.
记住了  别坐在软坐垫
Remember, do not sit on cushions,
地毯  任何泡沫或孔状物
carpets, anything foam, or porous.
要慢而淡定地说出他们的名字
Say their names slowly and calmly.
如果你感觉有东西在你的皮肤上蠕动
If you feel something crawling on you
别尖叫  轻轻晃动身体就好了
don't scream, just shake the body part lightly.
明白吗  我们开始吧
Okay? Let's do this.
-快点  -该死
- Come on. - Holy shit.
操
Fuck.
我得再等一会儿
I'm just gonna take another minute.
慢慢来
Take your time.
-你开玩笑吗  -待着别动
- You kidding me? - Stay there.
天啊
Oh, Jesus.
就一个该死的老妇人是吗
Just one fucking old lady, huh?
这不是芝加哥河一侧最强悍的恶霸
Well, if it isn't the toughest badass
专打基佬的牛逼人物嘛
fag beater this side of the Chicago River.
滚开
Fuck off.
我来给你看看乳房吧
I'll show you some tits.
穿菲奥娜的更合适些  不是吗
Fiona's fits better, doesn't it?
当然
Sure.
天啊
Oh My
你已经快弄完了  米奇
You're almost done, Mickey.
伊恩  搞毛啊
Ian, what the fuck?
我可以解释这个
I can explain this.
你他妈是谁啊
Who the hell are you?
我是儿童保护机构的布兰妮·特奇斯
I'm Britney Sturges from Child Protective Services.
她就直接走进来了
She just walked in.
太棒了
Yes!
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我差点淹死了一个荡妇
I totally almost drowned a slut!
她又踢又抓
She was kicking and scratching,
但我屏住呼吸  坚持着
but I held my breath and hung on
直到她昏过去
until she passed out!
天啊  你知道吗
Oh, my God. Guess what.
别他妈惹黛比·加拉格
You do not "F" With Debbie Gallagher!
别他妈惹我
Don't "F" With me.
小黛
Debs.
怎么了
Yeah. What?